Hello, welcome to class. Again, welcome. My name is David Brown and this is going to be an original combo reading writing and grammar class. I'm glad that you're all here. Have a seat everybody. Welcome.
大家好，欢迎来到课堂。再次欢迎。我叫戴维·布朗，这将是一堂独创的阅读、写作和语法综合课。我很高兴大家都在这里。请各位就座。欢迎。
Hey, Hector. How are you?
嘿，赫克托 (Hèkètuō)。你好吗？
Just fine. How are you?
我很好。您呢？
I'm doing great. Thank you.
我非常好。谢谢。
Welcome. Welcome.
欢迎。欢迎。
Thank you.
谢谢。
I see that you selected a class about arguments. Would you like to learn how to be more persuasive in today's class?
我看到您选择了一节关于论证的课。您想在今天的课上学习如何更具说服力吗？
I would like to. I would love to actually because that's a very important thing to do when you speak another language.
我想学。实际上我非常想学，因为当你说另一种语言时，这是一件非常重要的事情。
Yeah, the basic question of this is what do we want and how do we get that? And communication is the means in which we acquire the things that we want.
是的，这个问题的基本点是：我们想要什么，以及我们如何得到它？而沟通是我们获得我们想要的东西的手段。
So learning to be persuasive is just really an amazing soft skills to learn.
所以学习如何具有说服力确实是一项非常棒的软技能。
And there are procedures that we can follow in order to persuade effectively. So in today's lesson, we'll talk about persuading effectively and about some grammar reading and writing task that can help us to persuade formally.
并且有一些我们可以遵循的程序来有效地进行说服。所以在今天的课上，我们将讨论有效地进行说服，以及一些可以帮助我们进行正式说服的语法、阅读和写作任务。
We have this concept of cohesion and cohesion is when something is whole.
我们有这个“cohesion”（连贯性 liánguànxìng）的概念，连贯性是指某事物是完整的。
In order to make a good argument, we need to have all the parts of the argument.
为了做出一个好的论证，我们需要具备论证的所有部分。
And we also need the argument to be smooth. It has to flow. So we have cohesion and those two concepts that we'll talk about a little bit today.
而且我们还需要论证流畅。它必须有条理。所以我们有“cohesion”（连贯性）和“flow”（流畅性 liúchàngxìng）这两个概念，我们今天会稍微讨论一下。
So let's explore how we can achieve this.
那么，让我们探讨一下如何实现这一点。
So I have an image on the screen here. It says from jumbled ideas to a clear persuasive point.
屏幕上有一张图片。上面写着“从杂乱无章的想法到清晰有说服力的观点”。
We see this guy with a messy room.
我们看到这个人的房间很乱。
He's torn over curtain there.
那里的窗帘破了。
And it makes it look clean there.
而它让那里看起来很干净。
It actually looks like mine.
实际上看起来像我的房间。
All right, all right.
好的，好的。
We have our arguments are like this, right?
我们的论点就像这样，对吧？
Our arguments can be messy or they can be organized.
我们的论点可能杂乱无章，也可能条理清晰。
And if our arguments are presented in an organized way, then we're more likely to convince people that something is true.
如果我们的论点以有条理的方式呈现，那么我们就更有可能说服人们相信某事是真的。
We want to do this genuinely. How can we genuinely organize our ideas to make a persuasive point?
我们希望真诚地做到这一点。我们如何才能真诚地组织我们的想法，以提出一个有说服力的观点呢？
Let's see if you can remember something about arguments or tell me what you think you know about persuasion.
让我们看看你是否能记起一些关于论证的知识，或者告诉我你认为你对说服了解多少。
What are two parts of an argument that you remember?
你记得论证的哪两个部分？
Remember any specific parts?
记得任何具体的部分吗？
Actually, I can't remember it.
实际上，我记不起来了。
You know, like being so organized.
你知道，比如条理清晰之类的。
And let me see the other one.
让我想想另一个。
You said, organized.
你说过，条理清晰。
And messy.
和杂乱无章。
Okay.
好的。
And the opposite will be organized, right?
相反的就是条理清晰，对吧？
So being organized versus his versus messy.
所以是条理清晰对比杂乱无章。
How about the structure of an argument?
论证的结构怎么样？
How do you argue effectively?
你如何有效地进行论证？
What is something that you need to do in order to make a good argument?
为了做出一个好的论证，你需要做些什么？
Well, actually, I need to, I need to make it so comprehensive.
嗯，实际上，我需要，我需要让它非常全面。
Right? For the person that is.
对吧？对于那个人来说。
Listen to one argument. Right?
听一个论点。对吧？
And it has to be easy.
而且它必须容易。
To understand.
理解。
And easy to understand too.
而且也容易理解。
Agreed.
同意。
So if we improve some of these aspects of grammar, like cohesion and flow, we can make it easier to understand.
所以如果我们改进一些语法的方面，比如连贯性和流畅性，我们就能让它更容易理解。
We can make it organized and not messy.
我们可以让它条理清晰，而不是杂乱无章。
And we can make it whole. We can make it comprehensive.
我们可以让它完整。我们可以让它全面。
So these are our learning objectives for today's class.
这些是我们今天课程的学习目标。
Can you read this first objective for us?
你能为我们读一下第一个目标吗？
Yeah, learning objectives for today.
是的，今天的学习目标。
Analyze a model argument for structure and flow.
分析一个范例论证的结构和流畅性。
You want me to read all of them?
您要我把它们都读完吗？
Okay.
好的。
Utilize a graphic organizer to the construct arguments.
利用图形组织工具来构建论点。
Understand how grammatical choices impact clearly.
理解语法选择如何影响清晰度。
And cohesion.
和连贯性。
Practice using transitional device says effectively.
练习有效地使用过渡词语。
And identify and correct common errors affecting argument clearly.
并识别和纠正影响论证清晰度的常见错误。
Alright, let's practice two of these words here.
好的，让我们练习一下这里的这两个词。
This one is pronounced repeat after me clarity, clarity.
这个词发音是，跟我读，clarity, clarity。
Oh, clarity.
哦，clarity。
Okay.
好的。
And this one is with a Jen sound, like a Z.
这个词带有 Jen 的音，像 Z 一样。
ZJ kind of sound cohesion.
有点像 ZJ 的音，cohesion。
Cohesion and clarity.
Cohesion 和 clarity。
Okay.
好的。
Yeah, I didn't notice it was.
是的，我没注意到它是。
The word as with clear.
和 clear 一样的词。
I confuse it actually.
我实际上搞混了。
Yeah, it's related to the word clear.
是的，它和 clear 这个词有关。
So clear.
所以 clear。
Yeah, it's related.
是的，它们相关。
The same thing.
是同一个东西。
Right.
对。
That's what I think.
我是这么想的。
Uh huh.
嗯哼。
So you have clarity, which is the noun and something is clear.
所以你有 clarity 这个名词，而某物是 clear 的，
It's the adjective.
那是形容词。
Yeah.
是的。
Alright.
好的。
So what we can start off with first is the anatomy of an argument.
那么我们首先可以从论证的剖析开始。
The different parts of an argument.
论证的不同组成部分。
And this is something that we can learn.
这是我们可以学习的东西。
And remember from the days in school, when we would write essays and things like that.
并且回想一下在学校写论文之类的日子。
How do you structure an essay?
你如何构建一篇论文？
What comes first, next, and then last, when you write?
写作时，什么先来，什么其次，什么最后？
Let's read this part here.
让我们读一下这部分。
Can you read this paragraph for me?
你能为我读一下这段吗？
Sure.
当然。
A well crafted argument resembles a well engineered structure.
一个精心构建的论证类似于一个精心设计的结构。
It requires robust components and seamless connections.
它需要坚实的组成部分和无缝的连接。
Cohesion ensures ideas interlinked logically.
连贯性确保思想在逻辑上相互关联。
While fluency allows the reader to navigate the argument smoothly.
而流畅性则让读者能够顺畅地理解论证。
Okay, excellent.
好的，非常好。
So I made this image here to demonstrate this idea geometrically.
所以我做了这张图片来用几何方式展示这个想法。
So we have the idea that an argument is complete.
所以我们有这样一个想法：论证是完整的。
But an argument can be complete, but not flow well.
但是一个论证可以是完整的，但却不流畅。
An argument can have all of the parts, but they're not put together.
一个论证可以包含所有部分，但它们没有很好地组合在一起。
So if we look at each stage of this, we see that it starts with a few elements that are not connected very well.
所以如果我们看这个的每个阶段，我们会发现它开始于一些没有很好连接的元素。
They're not connected via the reasoning that we need.
它们没有通过我们需要的推理连接起来。
We see that it starts to form, but it doesn't have good flow.
我们看到它开始形成，但没有很好的流畅性。
And when the flow improves, we end with the perfect circle.
当流畅性得到改善时，我们最终得到一个完美的圆。
So this illustrates the idea of a cohesion, which is it being whole.
所以这阐释了连贯性的概念，也就是它的完整性。
The hexagon in this picture has cohesion, but it doesn't have flow.
这张图片中的六边形具有连贯性，但没有流畅性。
This circle, on the other hand, has cohesion and has flow.
而这个圆，则既有连贯性又有流畅性。
So how can we do that?
那么我们怎样才能做到呢？
How can we structure our paragraphs and our essays?
我们如何构建我们的段落和论文？
So that it is organized that it contains all of the parts that it needs.
使其有条理，包含所有需要的部分。
And so that it transitions from one part to the next logically.
并且使其从一部分到下一部分过渡合乎逻辑。
And if we do that right, if we do it effectively, then we have both of those elements and we strengthen our argument.
如果我们做得对，如果我们做得有效，那么我们就同时拥有了这两个元素，并加强了我们的论证。
So we have these argumentative elements, the puzzle pieces, cohesion, the connective structure, and the fluency, the smooth flow between ideas.
所以我们有这些论证元素，即拼图的各个部分；连贯性，即连接结构；以及流畅性，即思想之间的顺畅流动。
All right. So we need to remember these core components of an argument.
好的。所以我们需要记住论证的这些核心组成部分。
Let's read these here. Can you read these for me?
让我们读一下这些。你能为我读一下吗？
Sure. Can I read it from the very beginning?
当然。我可以从最开始读吗？
Like recall the core components of an argument, claim, actually, background, ceases,
比如回顾论证的核心组成部分：主张 (claim)，事实 (facts)，背景 (background)，论点 (thesis)，
topic sentences, evidence, examples, potential, rebuttal,
主题句 (topic sentences)，证据 (evidence)，例子 (examples)，潜在的反驳 (potential rebuttal)，
and conclusion, a solid grasp of this element is foundational.
和结论 (conclusion)。对这些元素的扎实掌握是基础。
Very good.
非常好。
So we have the claim. Another word for claim is a thesis.
所以我们有“claim”（主张）。“claim”的另一个说法是“thesis”（论点）。
We have the background, which is the context of what we're talking about.
我们有“background”（背景），也就是我们谈论内容的上下文。
If we start talking and we start arguing, but nobody knows what we're talking about with the background of it, then it's not clear.
如果我们开始谈论并开始论证，但没有人知道我们谈论的是什么，它的背景是什么，那么它就不清晰。
So we start with a claim.
所以我们从“claim”（主张）开始。
We can give us some background information about that.
我们可以提供一些关于它的背景信息。
And then we have our thesis statement.
然后我们有我们的“thesis statement”（中心论点陈述）。
This is a thesis statement that is basically the main argument of the entire thing we're trying to convince the other person to believe.
这是一个中心论点陈述，基本上是我们试图说服对方相信的整个事情的主要论点。
So to persuade is to convince someone else to believe something.
所以说服就是让别人相信某事。